http://www.communio-icr.com/legal/privacy

Communio, Inc., is committed to protecting the privacy of the personal information that you provide us when using our website.
Information We Collect
When you create an account, log on, or add products to your shopping cart, the website uses a “cookie.” Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored by your web browser on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies allow the website to store and reference specific types of information while you are visiting a site. Information collected is used on an aggregate basis only; for example, to tell us how visitors commonly use and navigate this site.
We use the personal information you submit only to assist us in fulfilling your order. This may include the following uses: To send e-mail acknowledgments of subscription order or correspondence conducted on the website; to notify you of renewal options; to process subscriptions, to verify your credit card data, and to send you a receipt.
Credit Card Security
Your credit card data is received and processed by the secure server of Elavon Services, Inc. Communio neither views nor retains any of this data.
Other
When you use www.communio-icr.com, you consent to our collection and use of the personal information you provide. Communio will never sell, rent, or give your personal information to any third party. If Communio is required by law or a legal process to release individual or organizational information, we must cooperate fully.
Policy Updates
Our privacy policy may change, so please check back from time to time.
Questions
If you have any questions or comments about this privacy statement, you may contact us at communio@aol.com, or by mail at PO Box 4557, Washington, DC, 20017, USA.
